- What's that?! - Very gross!
－這是什麼？ －嘩！噁心死了
- Wow! - Cool shot!
－嘩！　　　－正點啊
Are we there already?
咦？到了嗎？
Yes! Let's go
到了到了，下車！
Move!
走呀！
Funny...
怎麼啦？
Why do we stop here?
為什麼停車？
Bye
再見
Oh, shit!
天啊…
Oh, shit! You moron! How dare you taping this?
我靠！你找死啊？ 這種東西你也拍！
- Cut that out! - Okay, okay
－把它關掉！　　－是是是！
You heard me!
叫你關掉啊！
Give me some
我也要
This is the best time for horror stories
這種環境適合講鬼故事
Ever heard about the story of the All Souls' Day?
有沒有聽過一個 關於七月十四的鬼故事
Depends on which year's All Souls' Day, right?
七月十四有那麼多， 誰知你說是哪一個
Exactly!
就是嘛
There is this one concerning...
有沒有聽說過這個
...my friend's uncle who owns a newsstand
我朋友的舅舅是開報攤的
On the last All Souls' Day and...
今年七月十四
right at his stall, he has...
在自己報攤那裡
...an encounter!
見到了！
It was past 4 am.
那天四點多
Still dark
天還沒亮
He was piling the papers like usual
他就像平常一樣正在整理報紙
Hi there, Mr. Chan!
陳先生，你好！
Do me a favor!
幫個忙啊！
Call an ambulance
幫我叫救護車
Granny here...
這個婆婆…
She... she said she's not feeling well...
她…她說很不舒服…
How about that?! Scary?!
怎麼樣？是不是嚇到爆啊？
Hell no
小兒科
Listen to mine!
還是聽聽我的吧！
This story happened to the god-sister...
這個故事發生在我朋友的哥哥…
...of my friend's brother
…的乾妹妹身上
They lived at the Jordan Firemen's Quarter
他們一家人住在佐敦消防局宿舍裡
It was an evening 2 years ago
在兩年前的一個晚上
It was cold...
那天晚上很冷
...about 8 degrees Celsius
8度左右
The god-sister slept till 2am...
我朋友的哥哥的乾妹妹睡到兩點鐘
...only to hear people drilling outside
突然聽到操場有步操的聲音
She thought... how strange
她就覺得很奇怪啦
It's far too cold and early...
一個大冷天
...for the firemen to drill now
消防隊員沒有理由 這麼早就出操啊？
So she got up to take a look
於是，她就走出去看一看
Too bad she did
她不看還好
Because...!
一看就…！
One of the Japanese soldiers spotted her
她竟然被其中一個日本兵發現
He yelled at her...
那日本鬼子對著她大喝一聲
pulled out his samurai sword and...
把武士刀拔了出來
...charged right at her!
向她衝過去！
Was the girl killed?
那女孩子有沒有死掉？
Nah
那女的啊？
She went nuts afterwards though
她瘋了，進了精神病院
Listen!
喂喂喂！
There is this true story, super gross!
我聽過一個真人真事呢， 超恐怖啊！
A friend of mine was listening to a ghost story and...
我朋友在泰國聽著鬼故事吃魷魚絲
She died choking!
噎死了！
Cut down the snack or you'll die!
噎死你啊，吃那麼多！
Come on! Cheers... cheers!
來！乾杯！乾杯！
Your horror stories are all second-handed
你們的鬼故事不是朋友就是表弟的
Frankly, 'ever had an encounter before?
說真的，有親眼見過嗎？
You guys should read more often!
沒事的時候看看書嘛！
What's that?
什麼東東啊？
Huh?
怎麼了？
This is the 10 ways...
這本書記載了
...to encounter ghosts from Thai's ancient rites
泰國流傳的10種見鬼的方法
You can't find this book just anywhere
這可不是隨隨便便可以買得到的
One evening, I took the wrong bus
有天晚上我搭錯車
Then got off at the wrong stop
又下錯站
A book store was still open
剛巧一家書局還沒關門
So I went in for directions
就進去問路了！
Anyone in? Hello?
有沒有人啊？…哈囉？
THE TEN ENCOUNTERS
見鬼十法
Pay first and read later... hmm...
想看的話，就買回家裡去看…晤
How much is it?
這本書多少錢啊？
It's karma that brings you to this book
我看你跟這本書很有緣份
I'll give you a discount then
就便宜點賣給你
How about 500 bahts?
五百匹好了！
You must be kidding!
你這不是搶錢嗎！
Too cheap, aye?
嫌便宜啊？
Then pay me the full price
那麼照原價好了…晤…
Here's your 500
五百就五百吧！
Listen up, kiddo
哎！聽著，這本書
Don't you ever turn to the last page of the book
千萬別翻到最後一頁！
Or else misfortune will come to you!
看了會有不幸的事情發生啊！
You'll regret it if you don't believe me!
不相信，你一定會後悔的！
Still, I cannot avoid misfortune!
可是不幸的事情始終發生了！
Don't you ever turn to the last page!
千萬別翻到最後一頁
Fix Price: 100 bahts
定價︰一百匹
Sale Price: 50 baths? Bastard!
特價︰五十匹？我靠…！
Moron...
靠…好差勁耶！
Even an old man can fool you!
一個老頭子就能把你唬了！
Men, this book is no bullshit though
可是這書裡面的方法
The rituals are authentic
確實是有根據的
And I have 2 real-live cases on hand to back it up!
其中兩個方法 還有真人真事的個案呢！
The first one is 'the condemned cornea transplant'
第一是換死人眼角膜
The second one is for...
第二個呢
...women only - to attempt suicide while pregnant!
女人才行︰懷孕的時候去自殺
I think...
這兩個
...I've heard these 2 cases previously
我好像也聽過
Me too...
我也好像聽過…
You see?
對吧
What's this? Yoga?
哎？這幹什麼？瑜咖術啊？
It's "Peek-a-stoop", a Thai custom still practiced today!
是「倒頭栽」！ 泰人相信這樣可以見到鬼！
Chongkwai
長貴啊
What are the other ways?
還有些什麼其它的方法啊？
Let me see
我看看！
Comb your hair at midnight and...
這個是十二點整梳頭
...the ghost you desire will appear in the mirror
就會在鏡子裡看到你想看的鬼了
Next
還有啊
Gees... something wrong with his eyes?
幹嘛？他長針眼啊？
The book says
書上說啊
Smudge the graveyard soil over your eyes and...
用葬過死人的泥巴塗眼睛
...you'll be exposed to the world of the spirits!
就會看到鬼世界了！
Aren't there any... simpler and safer ways?
有沒有… 再簡單又安全一點的方法啊？
Sure! Simpler way...
有，簡單點嘛
Open an umbrella indoors
在屋裡打傘！
You'll score for sure!
保證見鬼
So you mean
你是說
If we follow the instructions
照著這些方法玩
...we'll get to see ghosts for sure
就一定能見到鬼了
It depends
也不一定
Different players have...
不同的人玩
...different success rates
有不同的成功率
Why not try it out then?
說到這裡，沒道理不試試看吧！
Damn right!
對啊對啊！
We sure need a game to get through the night!
不玩我們今夜怎麼過？對不對？
Well... why not?!
晤…就是嘛！
Given there are different success rates...
不是說有成功率嗎？
...we might not get to see them after all, right?
也就是…不一定見得到囉！啊？
...Right
…對啊
Then listen carefully
那麼你們聽清楚
Once the game has started
遊戲一旦開始了
You can't quit playing no matter what happens
無論中途發生了 什麼事也絕不可以停
Or else, misfortune will come to you
否則的話就會大禍臨頭
You've heard me
不怕死的話
Now let's begin!
現在就開始吧！
Let's try the most convenient way!
先試個最容易的！
Thai's "A Glass of Spirit"...
泰國人的杯仙
Chinese's "Plate Genie" & "Witchy Board" of the West...
跟中國人的碟仙、老外的巫師板
...are all alike
根本就是一模一樣
That is: Invite a ghost to spell out his messages
都是請鬼來在紙上把文字逐一指出來
Gees... it's moving...
哎呀…動了…動了
You moron! That's not funny!
討厭死了！你嚇人啊你！
- God... it's here! - Stop shuffling!
－來了…好害怕啊！ －不要再亂動啊！
Reak...
Reak…
chan...
Chan…
ma...
ma…
tum...
tum…
mai...
mai…
- Why are you calling me? - Ah!
－叫我有事嗎？　　　－嘩！！！
Hey!
喂！
Mom! Why are you still up?
媽啊！你幹嘛不睡啊？
You're scaring my friends!
這麼晚，嚇死我朋友啦！
Serves you right!
哼！你怎麼不說
You guys are killing my ears!
是我被你們吵死了呢！
It's late already! Go to bed now!
現在幾點了，還不去睡覺！
Okay, after you
我知道了，你先睡吧
Sorry guys
不好意恩
My mom did some heavy channeling last night
我媽昨天晚上 才幫人家做了一夜的法
She needs to rest... we'd better be quiet
她要休息，我們小聲一點！
So your mom is a spiritual medium?!
原來你媽是幫人家作法術的啊！
No wonder she looks kind of weird
怪不得樣子邪邪的…！
Late Dinner Alert
怪不得樣子邪邪的！
Thai people believe that...
泰國人相信
...crossroads emit a lot of negative power
十字路口是陰氣最盛
They are the favorite hangouts for stray spirits
孤魂野鬼最多的地方
To catch a glimpse of them
想看到他們
Go to an intersection after midnight with...
就要帶著三菜一湯、飯碗和筷子
...a meal for 3, bowls and chopsticks
在午夜之後找個十字路口等著
Our target...
我們的目標
...the hungry ghosts
是那些餓鬼
Tap the bowl with chopsticks and...
等一下要不停的敲你們的碗
...hungry ghosts will come for the food
那些餓鬼就會自動來吃飯了！
Is it really going to work?
真的會有效嗎？
Of course! Believe me, sure thing!
當然了！書是這樣說的！試試看
When you see them, don't scream, huh!
待會見到鬼，千萬不要叫啊
Look who's talking! Just don't flee before me!
你管你自己啦！ 待會你可不要嚇跑啊！
Once you start tapping the bowl, do not stop!
敲碗的時候，千萬不能停
If you stop, the ghosts will see you
停下來，那些鬼就會看到你！
You don't want to risk being possessed, okay?
鬼一上身就糟糕了知道嗎？
Let's roll!
開始吧
What is it?
幹嘛？
What's the matter?
什麼事？幹什麼嘛？
Stay cool, keep on tapping
冷靜點，繼續敲，別停
What did you see?
你看到什麼？
What is it?! What's going on?!
幹什麼？怎麼了？怎麼了？
I didn't see a thing!
沒有啊！
- What is it? - Did you see that?
－什麼啊？　　－有沒有看到？
Stay cool...!
冷靜點，冷靜點…
Keep tapping!
繼續敲不要停！
What?!
什麼啦？
- What's wrong? - What did you see?
－幹嘛！　　－你看到什麼了嘛
- What did you see? - What now?
－你看到什麼了嘛！ －啊？怎麼啦？
...I see "them"!
…我見到了！
Keep tapping!
繼續敲啊！不要停啊！
Stay cool! Tap!
冷靜冷靜！繼續敲！
What's wrong?!
什麼事啊？
Tap!
繼續敲！
I see nothing!
我什麼都沒見到啊！
Hey! I didn't get to see anything!
喂！我怎麼什麼都沒見到！
What is it that you see, Gofei?
你們見到什麼啦？高輝？
- Over there! - But there's nothing there!
－那邊… －那邊？我看不到什麼啊
It's not fair! Everybody got to see it except me!
為什麼你們通通都看到， 就我看不到？
Told you we all have different reception of ghosts
我不是說過每個人 對鬼的感應不一樣嘛
Maybe you're just the type who can't see them!
你可能是一輩子 都見不到鬼的那種人！
Chongkwai, are there any other ways?
長貴，還有沒有其它方法啊？
Don't you guys chicken out now!
你們不要翹頭啊！
I've got to see ghosts tonight!
我今天一定要見到鬼！
Play Hide n' Seek at midnight carrying a black cat
半夜抱黑貓玩捉迷藏， 鬼就會一起玩
Ghosts will come join us and...
鬼呢，會擋住我們其中一個
...block one of us from our view
讓我們看不到那個人
We then let go of the black cat
那個時候放出黑貓
The cat can make the ghost appear before us
黑貓就可以讓鬼現形
So, not only will we find that missing person
那麼我們不但可以找到那個人
We can also... see the ghost!
還可以…見鬼！
I quit! Come back out!
不玩了！快點出來吧！
I quit!
不玩了！
Papa! What's this stinky water? Papa...
爸爸！這是什麼水啊？爸爸…
Where is he?
找不到啊！
What now?
怎麼辦？
I think a ghost is blocking Kofei
有鬼擋著高輝，所以找不到
It's okay, it's okay... I'm letting the cat go now
不要怕，不要怕，我放貓啊…
Ebony, lead the way!
小黑帶路啊！帶路啊！
Kofei! Kofei!
高輝！高輝！…
- Kofei! - Over there!
－高輝！高輝！　　－前面呀！
Ebony... seems... dead!
小黑…好像…好像死掉了！
Even the cat is dead?
連貓都死了？
What do we do now?! What happened to Kofei?!
那現在怎麼辦啊？高輝怎麼辦呀？
What do we do?! Where the hell is he?!
現在怎麼辦啊？高輝到那兒去了？
- Kofei! - Kofei!
－高輝！…　　－高輝！…
Kofei, we quit the game! Come back out!
高輝！不要玩了！出來啦！
Kofei, call it off!
高輝不玩了！
- Kofei! - Kofei!
－高輝！…　　－高輝！…
Kofei!
高輝！
Hello? Kofei! Kofei!? Hello?
喂？高輝！高輝！？喂？
April, you okay? The phone didn't even ring!
怎麼啦April？ 不要嚇我，電話沒響過啊！
No, it did ring!
電話剛剛明明有響啊！
Don' worry too much! The police will follow
你別這樣啦，警察說會繼續找的啊！
We will find Kofei for sure!
一定會把高輝找回來的！
It's all you fault
全都是你害的
You'd better go back to Hong Kong first
你們先走吧，回香港等消息吧！
The police might not be able to help this time
有些事情，警察也幫不上忙
- But auntie... - Just listen to me
伯母可是…　　－不要再說了
Leave while you still can
可以走就最好趕快走
Someone could be setting you up
只怕有人不甘願
I don't think you can defend yourselves!
要跟你們玩下去，那就槽了！
THE EYE MASK
要跟你們玩下去，那就槽了
April!
April！
Don't!
不要啊！
April, are you okay?
April！你怎麼樣啊？
April! Close your eyes, don't open them, not now!
April 閉上眼睛！千萬別張開…
Close them tight... listen to me!
眼睛閉上，聽我說
You'll be in trouble if you open them now!
現下張開眼會出事啊！
We're here for you! You'll be okay!
不要怕！是我們啦！沒有事的！
Hold on for just one more sec
你再等一等…
Okay, now you can open your eyes
好！行了！可以張開眼
- Hey, April! - April, 'you all right?
喂，April！　　－怎麼了April？
It hurts!
好痛啊！
It was so scary! My eyes, they fell out!
好可怕！ 我眼睛掉了！我眼睛掉了
No way
開玩笑嘛
Your eyes are still there
你眼睛還在啊
Don't worry, everything's okay now!
沒事了！別害怕，什麼事都沒了
You guys were only lucky to save her in time!
還好，你們還來得及去救她回來
She almost slipped into the limbo world!
剛才很危險啊！ 她差一點就進冥界去了
If she did, she'd be trapped forever!
進去之後就出不來了！
Chongkwai! You should know better not to play with fire!
長貴！你不是小孩子， 做人要負責任！
You're not a child anymore!
你們什麼東西不好玩？
What did auntie say?
伯母說什麼？
Does she know where Kofei is?
是不是知道高輝在那裡啊？
My mom blamed me for teaching you...
我媽在怪我
...the usage of graveyard soil
教你用屍泥塗眼睛
I nearly caused you trapped in the limbo world
害妳差一點掉入冥界
I'm so sorry
對不起啊！
I never thought things would turn out like this!
我沒想過會搞成這樣！
There're too many things that you don't notice
你們不懂的事情太多了
There are other dimensions in this world!
這個世界不同的空間
Do you understand?
你們懂嗎？
Apart from our human world...
除了我們人的陽界，鬼的冥界
...there are numerous unknown dimensions
還有很多很多我們不知道的空間
April was lucky not to slip into the limbo world
ApriI啊， 還好你剛才沒有掉進冥界去
When I was a kid, I saw this young woman
在我小時候， 就親眼見過一個女孩子
She entered the limbo world by mistake
她不小心，走進了陰界！
Let me out! Let me out!
放我出去！放我出去！
Now you know!
以後要記住
Always stay away from black magic
玩這種東西，是非常危險的
When things get out of hand...
出了事情的話
...you won't be able to survive the consequences
你們誰也應付不了！知道嗎？
But where is Kofei now?
那現在高輝到那兒去了？
Who knows?
不知道
Just don't stay here! Go back to Hong Kong now!
我不是說過不要留在這裡嗎？ 回香港吧！
No, I won't! I won't leave without Kofei!
不行！我不回去！ 我要留下來找高輝
Cous
表姐
Wouldn't it be kind of low if we leave?
就這樣走了，是不是太沒道義呢？
If we leave, yes, it is low
這樣子走掉，真的是沒道義
Then we shouldn't do this!
絕對不可以做出這種事情！
But then...
可是…
...the cab is here already
車已經來了
Low or not low... we can discuss that on the way!
道義氣這東西…上了車再說吧！
Scumbags! How could they ditch April like this?!
臭孩子！一點道義都沒有
You call them your friends?!
丟下April 就跑掉了！
I didn't talk to Ted after we're back to Hong Kong
回到香港我就沒有跟得仔聯絡了
He didn't call me either
他也沒有找我
Maybe he just wants to forget about what happened
可能大家都想把泰國的事忘了吧
Me too
我也想
But I know it's not possible
可是我知道是不可能的
For the first two weeks, Chongkwai did call
回來那幾個禮拜， 長貴還有打電話來
I didn't dare ask him about April though
可是我不太敢問他 April 的事
I wonder how she is now...
不知道她現在怎麼樣了
I pretend everything's normal... I go to school
我就裝的像正常一樣 繼續上課、下課
I play, I eat, I went out
逛街、吃飯囉
Damn right, everything is normal
對哦，如果真的很正常
So what am I pretending?
又何必要裝呢？
Mister!
先生！
Anyone in?
有沒有人啊？
"The Ten Encounters"...
見鬼十法…
A GLASS OF SPIRIT
杯仙
That man has gotta have something to do with Kofei!
那男人跟高輝失蹤的事一定有關
He even drew the 5 of us playing the damn game!
他還在書裡畫了 我們五個人玩杯仙呢！
Bonehead!
笨蛋！
It's obvious that he's cast a spell on all of you!
他啊，明明就是給你下了降頭！
You guys just can't overcome this on your own!
這個劫， 你們幾個是絕對沒辦法解的！
Midnite comb
午夜梳頭
THE FORBIDDEN shade
室內打傘
What's wrong with you?!
幹什麼？嚇死人啊？
It's only a ball!
球你也怕！
Peek-a-stoop
倒頭栽
It's disturbing! Just answer it! Maybe it's urgent!
震得桌子都動了！ 接吧，說不定有急事！
Okay!
好！
Teddy? This time I really saw it!
得仔啊！這次是真的， 真的見鬼啦！
You saw ghosts again? Where is it this time?
又見鬼啊？這次在那裡看到的啊？
Right outside my front door!
在家裡門口啊！
Have a drink and you won't remember it
不要想那麼多， 喝喝酒，很快就忘了
Don't play dumb anymore-it's no use!
你不要再裝了，騙不了自己的！
There is really a ghost playing ball right outside!
真的有隻鬼在我們家門口打球啊
Just come over now!
你馬上給我回來啊
Are... are you sure?
你是不是眼花啊…？
100 percents!
你才眼花呢
I did the Peek-a-stoop bending over and I saw "him"!
我剛才按長貴說的 倒著頭才看得到他啊！
I am so very sure!
難道還會有錯嗎？
Then... I... then...
那…我…那…
Cut the crap and come over now!
還那什麼，馬上給我回來啊！
Okay, I will
我知道了！
Well, I must go...
我先走了…
Where' you going?
你去哪啊？
May? It's Chongkwai! April has vanished!
阿美？長貴啊！April 失蹤了？
What?
呀？
Already 2 people among us have disappeared
你們沒事吧？ 我們已經有兩個人出事了
My mom wants you guys to be careful!
我媽叫你跟得仔千萬要小心啊
Why is it still so crowded so late at night?
這麼晚電梯還這麼擠？
Mister, have you seen my report card?
哥哥，你有沒有看到我的成績單？
You little damn thing!
嗯！你這小鬼！
Sorry
對不起啊
I thought you were a ghost!
我以為你是鬼啊！
Don't cry... I'm sorry!
不要哭…對不起哦！
So what if there are ghosts?
哪來這麼多的鬼啊？
Messing with us?
找死？
What' you doing?!
幹什麼？
Where am I?!
這是什麼地方？
It's dangerous here
進來再說
Teddy...!
嗚…得仔啊！
Thank god you're here!
你來了就好了！嗚…
Don't cry... come sit down first
喂！你不要哭了， 坐下來再說…來！
We are dead meat
我們這次真的死定了
I see ghosts all the time!
我們見鬼了
Our problem has not ended just there in Thailand
我看泰國的事情還沒完
Remember what Chongkwai said?
你記不記得長貴說過
Once we've started the game
只要一開始玩這個遊戲
We just can't quit playing until it's all over!
不管中途 發生什麼事情都不可以停啊！
Looks like we must return to Thailand...
嘩！鬧得這麼嚴重
...before we can settle everything
要回泰國找長貴才能搞得定
Ai? Where's that girl?
哎？那個女的呢？…
What are you looking for?
你在找什麼？
My Friend, the girl who came in with me!
我朋友啊！ 跟我一起進來那個女孩子啊！
The one from Thailand!
你記不記得
We share the same ride together, remember?
在泰國那個啊！ 跟我們一起坐車那個啊
It's okay now! Come out!
喂！沒事了！出來吧
I think... I only saw you...
可是…可是從頭到尾
...coming in alone!
我只看到你一個人進來啊
Why are you watching these tapes?
你幹嘛看這些帶子？
Don't tell me...
你不要跟我說…
...she's here!
她已經進來了！
But... I can't see her now!
可是我現在看不到她啊！
Wanna try and look between your legs?
你要不要試試倒著頭看一下？
But how?
怎麼看啊？
BEND-
倒…
O-
頭…
- VER
看！
We shouldn't be doing this! Too risky!
我們這樣做很危險啊！
Our lives are at stake anyway!
難道要我們這樣等死嗎？
This method could be our last resort!
我就拚死試最後這個辦法， 看會怎樣！
Cousin
表姐啊
Let's think it over!
還是看一看再說嘛！
You're not in this with me, right? Suit yourself!
你不去是嗎？我不會勉強你的！
Wait!
哎呀
That's not what I mean
我不是這個意思喇
I'm in
我陪你去
To advance your death
到冥界去
You have to play dead wearing a used funeral suit...
要穿上一套死人穿過的壽衣裝死
...and then you can infiltrate the limbo world
你們只有一柱香的時間
Your time there is limited and you must leave on time
到時候， 我會用招魂鈴聲叫你們走的
Once you hear me ringing a bell...
你們一聽到鈴聲
...enter the stream of white light right away!
馬上跟著白光走！千萬不要等啊
It's your only way out; don't stall
不然的話，香燒完了
Or you'd never come back!
你們就回不來了！
Darn...
完了…
I still can't fall asleep
還是睡不著
What a drag...
怎麼辦呢…
Well then...
那麼…
...let me help you!
我幫你！
- Where are we? - Don't know
－我們去了那裡啊？ －我哪知道
Darn...
完了…
- I'm kind of scared - I...
－我有點怕耶…　　－我…
...I'm scared too!
…也怕耶！
Wait!
喂！
A ghost!
鬼啊！！
But he is smiling!
他還對我們笑呢！
That's right! Chongkwai said...
對啊！長貴說過
If we don't meddle with them, they won't bother us!
我們不惹那些鬼， 他們就不會來惹我們
This one is kind of cute!
還蠻可愛的嘛
Hey, they seem quite friendly too!
你看他們對我們也蠻友善的哦
There
喂
Up there!
上面！
Something's not right! It's getting crowded here!
不對勁耶！好像越來越多鬼啊！
And they aren't smiling; not so friendly either
這邊的不笑了也不太友善耶！
Quick, think of something!
哎！快想個辦法啦！
Cannot!
我想不到啊！
Has Chongkwai ever said that...
記不記得長貴說過
...ghosts are afraid of the verve in our breath?
他們會怕我們的陽氣啊！
He said that?
是嗎？
Well...
唔！
Gee, it works!
哎！真的可以啊
Man, you stink!
喂！你好臭啊！
Get up! Let's go!
起來！走啦
They've stopped hunting us
嘿！沒有再追來了
How' you doing, Ted?
得仔你怎麼樣？
I need to rest!
我要休息一下
So do I
我也是…
Be careful, cousin!
小心啊表姐！
You found me, how boring! I quit!
還是被你們找到了， 沒意思，我不玩了
Kofei!
高輝！
Thank god you're alright! We've finally found you!
你沒事太好了！ 我們終於找到你了
Calm down, girl! You didn't see me for only an hour!
喂！才一下子不見， 幹嘛哭成這樣子？
Where were you guys?
你們到那裡去了？
- Listen! You were gone for a month! - A month?!
－不！你已經失蹤一個月啦 ─一個月？
We messed up!
我們出事了！
A ghost has blocked you from our view all these while
你被小鬼擋住， 我們整一個月都找不到你
We play dead to come here for you in the limbo world
所以我和表姐啊裝死人， 來冥界找你
Huh? This is...
呀？冥界…
This is the limbo world?
這裡…是冥界？
Yes!
對啊
It's all over! I'm darn pooped
完了！我真的沒有氣了
Same here
我也沒了…
Kofei, you're new here
高輝，你是新來的
Greet them with your breath!
你放點陽氣嚇他們啊！
My breath?
陽氣？
Yes!
是啊
What... do you mean?
怎…怎麼放啊？
They're afraid of it
他們會怕的！
But how?
要怎麼放嘛！
I really can't do this anymore! I'm breathless!
我真的不行了！我真的沒有氣了
Show them your specialty!
你還不出絕招？
You can still fart, can't you?
你還有沒有屁放啊！呀？
Kofei!
高輝！
- Where are you? - April?
－你在那裡啊？　　─April ？
- I've come to stay with you! - April?!
－我來陪你啊！　　─April ？
- Kofei! - It's April!
－高輝！　　－是April 啊！
April! I'm here!
April ，這裡啊！
Kofei? Is that you?!
高輝？是不是你啊
Yes! It's April!
真的是 April 啊！
- Kofei! - April!
－高輝！　　─April！
Come with me now! Hurry!
喂！快點跟我走！快點啊
Don't look back!
跟來了…
You hear that?
聽到沒有啊？
I do!
有啊
Do you hear that? We are safe now!
聽到沒有，我們這下有救了
- It's Chongkwai! - It is!
－是長貴啊！　　－是啊！
What about him?
什麼長貴啊？
He said, run to the white light once we hear the bell
長貴說聽到了鈴聲然後跟著白光走
And we'd be out of here!
就可以走出去了！
Really?
是嗎？
Yes!
是啊
There it is! Let's go to the light now!
真的有白光耶！我們走吧！走啊
What white light? What bell?
什麼鈴聲什麼白光啊？
How come I don't hear or see any of these?
為什麼我什麼都聽不到， 看不到呢？
How did you come here?
你怎麼會到這裡來的？
Kofei
高輝
I thought you were dead
我以為你已經死了
That's why I...
所以我才會…
Mom! We're running out of time! Do something!
媽！香快燒完了怎麼辦啊？
Cous, what do we do now? Are we leaving or not?
表姐，現下怎麼辨啊？ 我們走不走啊？
Hey!
喂！
You guys go ahead! I'm staying!
你們走吧！我留下來
Just go!
走啦！
Auntie!
伯母
Chongkwai!
長貴！
Teddy!
得仔！
I told you
我早就說過了
This is a curse you can't overcome!
你們鬥不過他的！
The Ten Encounters
見鬼十法
A GLASS OF SPIRIT
杯仙
Interested in this book?
對這本書有興趣？
What if I give you a discount?
那麼我便宜點賣給你吧
You like that?
好不好？唔…